Now, what we can do is we can finally start styling our application.
现在我们终于可以设定应用样式了
So what we're going to do is we're going to go back and
我们将回去对一开始没有设定样式的组件
style all of the components that we initially didn't style.
进行样式设置
There are a few different ways to approach this.
可以采取几种不同的方式来设定样式
If you are comfortable with flexbox or if you just want a challenge,
如果你能熟练创建 flexbox 或者想要挑战下
go ahead and try to do this on your own.
可以自己尝试一下
And then once you do that, you can come back and watch me do it,
尝试之后 可以回来看看我的步骤
or you can just skip this entirely.
或者跳过整个视频
If you're not super comfortable,
如果不太熟练
then you can go ahead and watch me go through it.
可以观看我的步骤
So the very first thing we're going to do is in App.js,
首先我们将打开 App.js 文件
the only style we're going to add here is we're
在此文件中 我们唯一要设定的样式是
going to give this parent view a flex of one.
将此父视图的 flex 设为 1
The reason we're doing that is we're saying we
这么设置的原因是
want this component to take up all the available space,
希望此组件占用所有可用空间
so that way, any children components will be able to expand the full size of the phone.
这样的话 任何子组件都将能够展开为整个手机屏幕尺寸
Without this, that wouldn't be possible.
不这么设置的话 就无法实现这一点
Next, let's go ahead and style all of
接着 我们将对
the components inside of our getMetricMetaInfo function.
getMetricMetaInfo 函数中的所有组件设置样式
So to do this, let's go ahead, and up here,
转到此处
let's import StyleSheet, and then we're also going to import some more colors.
导入 StyleSheet 还需要导入一些颜色
Say, red, orange, blue,
例如 red、orange、blue
light purple, as well as pink.
lightPurp 以及 pink
And then now, what we can do is down here,
然后在下面
let's go ahead and create some styles.
创建一些样式
We're going to use the StyleSheet.create API.
我们将使用 StyleSheet.create API
And let's just go ahead and we'll have iconContainer.
输入 iconContainer
So this is going to be the container around the icon or this view right here.
它将是图标（即这里的视图）的容器
So what we want to do is,
我们将
let's go ahead and give it a padding of five.
padding 设为 5
We'll say borderRadius.
将 borderRadius
Let's give that eight.
设为 8
Width and height are going to be set to 50.
Width 和 height 设为 50
We want everything inside of it to be aligned on
其中的所有内容
the main axes in the center as well as the cross axes.
都沿着主轴和横轴居中
And then we'll just give it a marginRight of 20 pixels.
marginRight 设为 20 像素
So now, what we can do is,
然后
let's go ahead and select every view inside of this document,
选中此文件中的所有视图
and we will give it this iconContainer styles,
为其设定这一 iconContainer 样式
but we're also going to give it something else.
同时设定其他样式
So we can pass style in array.
我们可以向数组中传入样式
The first styles that are going to be added to this component is our iconContainer,
首先向此组件添加样式 iconContainer
which is coming from styles.iconContainer.
来自于 styles.iconContainer
And then what we want to do is we want to have
然后让每个组件
each of these have their own background color.
都具有自己的背景颜色
So let's come up here, and we'll say backgroundColor,
在这里输入 backgroundColor
and we will just give all of them red for now.
暂时都设为 red
So getIcon for running,
将跑步的 getIcon
let's go ahead and set that to red.
设为 red
And then for biking,
然后将骑车图标
let's set this to orange.
设为 orange
For swimming, we'll say blue.
将游泳图标设为 blue
For sleeping, we will say light purple.
将睡眠图标设为 lightPurp
And then finally, we will say pink.
最后一个设为 pink
So let's go ahead and take a look at what this looks like now.
我们看看应用界面的显示效果
So it looks like we have a typo.
似乎有个拼写错误
alignItem should be alignItems up here inside of our styles. All right.
在上面的 styles() 中 alignItem 应该为 alignItems
So you'll notice here, this looks pretty good,
可以看出一切看起来挺不错的
but instead of having black as the actual icon color,
但是我们希望实际图标颜色为白色
what we want to do is we want this to be white.
而不是黑色
And we just did this initially so that we could see the icon on the black background.
一开始这么设置是为了在黑色背景中看到这些图标
So let's go ahead and set that to white, and again,
我们将 color 改为 white
the reason we can type white as a variable is because we've imported it right here.
我们能将 white 当做变量是因为在这里导入 white 了
And then now, notice that we have these icons,
现在可以看到这些图标
and the icons themselves are white.
图标本身的颜色是白色